<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Posts on Shower Review</title><link>https://shower-review.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Shower Review</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 23:22:46 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shower-review.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Church Street Hotel London</title><link>https://shower-review.com/posts/church-street-hotel-london/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 23:22:46 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://shower-review.com/posts/church-street-hotel-london/</guid><description>Pressure ⭐⭐⭐⭐ Temperature ⭐⭐⭐⭐ Shower Head ⭐⭐⭐⭐ Mechanism ⭐⭐⭐ Church Street Hotel is a beautifully decorated hotel in an unassuming part of Camberwell, London which for some reason brings up prescription drug spam when you Google it. Similar to Generator, the bathroom was tiled however unlike there the shower was closed off with a glass door and a basin, like you would expect.
The day I was there was incredibly warm so my idea of good temperature might be skewed, but the pressure was absolutely fine and the shower was perfectly usable other than the mechanism being a little bit annoying.</description></item><item><title>Generator London</title><link>https://shower-review.com/posts/generator-london/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 23:10:29 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://shower-review.com/posts/generator-london/</guid><description>Pressure ⭐⭐⭐⭐ Temperature ⭐⭐⭐ Shower Head ⭐⭐ Mechanism ⭐⭐⭐ Generator is a hotel for trendy-but-poor 20-somethings offering rooms with up to 12 other random strangers in from around £20/night.
The regular clientele probably only comes back to the dorm to pass out after a long night of drinking in the ground-floor bar. Since my plans for the night were to watch YouTube on my laptop in my underwear I opted for the single room.</description></item><item><title>Arriva Hotel London</title><link>https://shower-review.com/posts/arriva-hotel-london/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 23:00:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shower-review.com/posts/arriva-hotel-london/</guid><description>Pressure ⭐ Temperature ⭐⭐⭐⭐ Shower Head ⭐ Mechanism ⭐⭐ The Arriva Hotel is situated just 6 minutes from King&amp;rsquo;s Cross station which is about the only redeeming feature except for the price. Trip advisor reviews describe the hotel as &amp;ldquo;very basic&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;like a 60s B&amp;amp;B only worse&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;old and smelly&amp;rdquo;. But we don&amp;rsquo;t care about that, how was the shower?
The shower cubicle was pretty badly stained and had clearly been installed quite some time ago.</description></item><item><title>Yotel Shoreditch</title><link>https://shower-review.com/posts/yotel-shoreditch/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 12:36:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shower-review.com/posts/yotel-shoreditch/</guid><description>Pressure ⭐⭐ Temperature ⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐ Shower Head ⭐⭐ Mechanism ⭐⭐⭐⭐ &amp;ldquo;Yotel&amp;rdquo; is a rather cringily named indie hotel chain, situated here in the equally cringey district of Shoreditch in London. Yotel focuses on making incredibly tiny hotel rooms feel less cramped than they really are, which they succeed at doing.
The shower in the room was a dual head, with one large fixed head above and a smaller detachable shower head below it.</description></item><item><title>Holiday Inn Express Birmingham</title><link>https://shower-review.com/posts/holiday-inn-express-birmingham/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 22:34:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://shower-review.com/posts/holiday-inn-express-birmingham/</guid><description>Pressure ⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐ Temperature ⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐ Shower Head ⭐⭐⭐⭐ Mechanism ⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐ This Holiday Inn Express is right in Birmingham city centre, and has absolutely no customer parking available. This isn&amp;rsquo;t a parking review, though, so I&amp;rsquo;m going to ignore that.
The hotel seems to have been built around 2016, making it at most 6 years old. Which is why it&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that the showers in this place are immaculate. The surfaces were so pristine I felt like I was the first person to ever step foot into that shower.</description></item></channel></rss>